adultinc.com 2018-08-16

# Privacy Policy of Adultinc - Adultinc

”[Adultinc](https://adultinc.com/)” refers to the website located at url address [https://adultinc.com](https://adultinc.com/), any subsequent url address to which this website redirects users, as well as all web sites, url’s and associated websites. The term “user” comprises all users of the website.

We publish the present privacy policy because we want to create a safe and transparent context for our users and we treat with seriosity and responsibility the way in which the personal data that comes to our possession are protected and used. The privacy policy describes the way in which Adultinc handles information and data supplied by users.

The methods that we use for collecting and sharing information and entirely presented and described in the present document. The way in which your personal data will be collected, recorded, stored or transferred are entirely conformed to the dispositions of the present Privacy Policy.

If you do not wish to adhere to the clauses of the present Privacy Policy, please leave Adultinc, since continuing to use the Adultinc services represents your full and unconditional agreement of respecting without exception the rules within the Privacy Policy. The present conditions are applied to all persons accessing or using the website.

If you do not partially or fully accept the stipulations of the Adultinc Privacy Policy or if you accessed the website by mistake, without the intention of accepting the Privacy Policy of Adultinc or you do not have the capacity of fully understanding or accepting the clauses of the Privacy Policy of Adultinc, please leave this website immediately and do not use Adultinc products.

## 1\. Protecting data and privacy

We try to keep the data you give us in safety conditions. Logistically speaking, we take all physical, electronic and administrative measures that can be reasonably taken, in order to maintain the security of the collected information. We do out best to limit the number of people with access to the database, as well as the usage of electronic security systems and the password to ensure protection against unauthorized access. We implemented security policies and adequate technical measures to maintain security regarding all personal data that is in our possession, to prevent any access or unauthorized modification, destruction, loss, and well as against any other illegal form of processing.

Nevertheless, the safety of transmitting data on the internet cannot be 100% guaranteed. Even in the context in which we use all necessary means for ensuring the security of the information you sent through the website, [Adultinc](https://adultinc.com/) cannot guarantee that the respective information will not be intercepted by third-parties. We will make sure, however, that any unauthorized transactions or activities will be traced and sanctioned according to the law.

Any data with personal character will be stored and used by the website respecting the legal dispositions regarding the protection of persons with respect to using personal data and the free circulation of the respective data.

Any other kind of messages or materials that you transmit on the website, such as questions, comments, suggestions or other messages of the kind will be considered as non-confidential and will not be subjected to any protection. Moreover, Adultinc will not take any responsibility for the situations in which the user publishes any personal data, at its own initiative, in a public message, on the Adultinc website.

## 2\. Storing and using the information

In order to fully use the services offered by Adultinc registering, or creating an account, is necessary. Users will be asked to fill in a form on the website, offering at least the following data and information:

  * full name and surname
  * complete residence address
  * valid email address
  * username
  * password
  * phone number
  * various information about user preferences

Any available information, such as an IP address, can be registered during access time. This information is used solely to help improve our services. Monitoring browser sessions only takes place in order to see what parts of the website might require adjustments and improvements and, on the other hand, to see the settings that work best. This kind of information mostly keeps users anonymous and are not classified as personal data, and are only meant to help us understand users’ desires and preferences.

Adultinc will store the data that you transmit to us when registering to use our online services, our client assistance service or technical support. The information is stored in our database. When personal data is collected, stored and used by our pages, this is always done by respecting the legal dispositions regarding the protection of persons in respect with using personal data and the free circulation of the respective data.

[Adultinc](https://adultinc.com/) will be able to transmit the collected data to partner websites, websites belonging to the same group or partners that are explicitly agreed upon, partners that help us provide you with the products and services that we offer or that create, operate and maintain our website from the exterior. These external companies agree to keep the privacy of all information shared with them and to use the information only to fulfill their respective obligations.

Adultinc will also be able to use your personal data to contact you, will be able to store and use personal data to send information about new offers, promotions, advertising and direct marketing messages. In case you wish to be contacted no more or you want to modify any information provided by us, you can request this directly at the email address contact@adultinc.com.

Personal data could be given to authorities upon their request in order to perform verifications imposed by the law, should it be required according to present, valid laws.

## 3\. Cookies

A cookie is the information sent by a website and saved on your computer’s hard disk. Adultinc might transmit you both temporary and permanent cookies. This website uses its own cookies, as well as third-party ones in order to better understand your needs and improve products and services, besides providing visitors with a much better navigating experience and services that are adapted to everyone’s interests. Cookies help us remember when you revisit our website. They can contain information such as logging data, for instance your email address or username. Your personal data can also be used to personalize as much as possible the services of Adultinc, as well as for marketing purposes.

Cookies play an important part in facilitating the access and delivering multiple services that the user enjoys on the Internet, such as:

  * cookies offer website owners with valuable feedback on the way their websites are used, so that they can make the websites more efficient and accessible to users
  * they allow multimedia applications or other website applications to be included in a certain website in order to create a more valuable, useful and pleasant navigating experience
  * they boost the efficiency of online advertising

The cookies of third-parties on this website can come from the following entities: Doubleclick.com, Facebook.com, Google Analytics, Google Adsense, as well as from the beneficiaries of advertising services provided by our society at a certain point through the website. Adultinc has no access to these cookies and cannot control them either.

## 4\. Communicating by e-mail

You will be contacted by us through email in order to receive offers, promotions or when communicating possible prizes that you won or with any other occasion that we must contact you. If you do not want to receive emails from us, please communicate this at the email address [contact@adultinc.com](mailto:contact@adultinc.com) or you can choose the „unsubscribe” option, available on our website. Please give us 10 working days from the moment we receive your request to finish the unsubscription process, since some of our promotions might have already been running at the time of your request.

## 5\. Spoofing and phishing

A common scam on the Internet is know as spoofing or phishing. This happens when you receive an email from an apparently legitimate source that asks you for personal information. Please be aware of the fact that we will never send you emails asking you to confirm personal data. If you ever receive an email that apparently comes from us, asking for that information, do not reply and do not click any email link that might appear in the email.

## 6\. Changes in the privacy policy

[Adultinc](https://adultinc.com/) reserves the right to modify or replace at any time the content of the privacy policy, with or without a preliminary notice of the user. The new conditions become applicable the moment they were introduced on the website and do not have retroactive effects.

Any modification, no matter how substantial, as well as the replacement of the privacy policy are fully at the discretion of Adultinc.

Please verify and reread these stipulations regularly, considering that any modifications will be immediately applicable once posted on the website. Using the website after their posting will be considered as a tacit acceptance of the modifications.
